<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page title="Donate to Chiba" id="donation">

    <subtitle>Support the Chiba project</subtitle>
    <para id="dear">
        Dear Chiba user,
    </para>
    <para>
        Thank you for your interest in Chiba. As you might know by now Chiba provides a free, standard-conformant
        Open Source XForms processor for everybody to use in their own applications. We're strongly believe that
        XForms has the potential to open new levels of productivity for data capturing and form-processing applications.
        We also believe that there's a strong need for an Open Source implementation to help spreading this technology
        and for security sensitive applications. Two developers are working full-time on Chiba to push it forward
        to a fully-conformant, production-quality implementation. Nearly three years lifetime, a growing community
        and over 10.000 downloads prove that we're taking this job seriously.
    </para>
    <para>
        If you're already using or think of using Chiba please consider helping us to succeed by making a donation.
        We'll use this money directly to improve the code and support the community.
    </para>
    <para>
        Thank you very much.
    </para>

    <para>
        <table border="0" cellpadding="10">
            <tr>
                <td width="50"></td>
                <td align="center">
                    <p>Click the button below to donate an amount of your choice.</p>
                    <form  action="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr" method="post">
                    <input type="hidden" name="cmd" value="_xclick" />
                    <input type="hidden" name="business" value="joern.turner@chibacon.de" />
                    <input type="hidden" name="item_name" value="Chiba project" />
                    <input type="hidden" name="cn" value="your note?" />
                    <input type="hidden" name="currency_code" value="EUR" />
                    <input type="hidden" name="tax" value="0" />
                    <input class="donation-button" type="image" src="https://www.paypal.com/en_US/i/btn/x-click-but04.gif" border="3" name="submit" alt="Make payments with PayPal - it's fast, free and secure!" />
                    </form>
                </td>
            </tr>
        </table>
    </para>

    <para>
        If you have any question regarding donations to Chiba or prefer others channels you may contact us <a href="mailto:joern.turner@users.sourceforge.net">here</a>
    </para>

</page>
